[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "How likely is it this will go to the very top of the legal system in America?", "question_tokens": ["How", "likely", "is", "it", "this", "will", "go", "to", "the", "very", "top", "of", "the", "legal", "system", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Well I had I think it was a victory for the fourth amendment, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "had", "I", "think", "it", "was", "a", "victory", "for", "the", "fourth", "amendment", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "Has Edward Snowden been vindicated by this ruling?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "Edward", "Snowden", "been", "vindicated", "by", "this", "ruling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Well, I think he's been proven right in terms of his views of this program.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "been", "proven", "right", "in", "terms", "of", "his", "views", "of", "this", "program", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edward Snowden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "ORGAN: How should he have responded then, if he was there reading about all this feeling concerned it breached American's constitutional rights, what else should he have done?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "How", "should", "he", "have", "responded", "then", ",", "if", "he", "was", "there", "reading", "about", "all", "this", "feeling", "concerned", "it", "breached", "American", "'s", "constitutional", "rights", ",", "what", "else", "should", "he", "have", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Well, you know, I'm not going to argue against the fact that he brought a lot of things to light.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "argue", "against", "the", "fact", "that", "he", "brought", "a", "lot", "of", "things", "to", "light", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edward Snowden"]}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "And may I supposed you think if Snowden was to give back the substantial data that he so far not revealed in return for an amnesty would that be a sensible conclusion to this given this court ruling today?", "question_tokens": ["And", "may", "I", "supposed", "you", "think", "if", "Snowden", "was", "to", "give", "back", "the", "substantial", "data", "that", "he", "so", "far", "not", "revealed", "in", "return", "for", "an", "amnesty", "would", "that", "be", "a", "sensible", "conclusion", "to", "this", "given", "this", "court", "ruling", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "IN", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "I would need a lot -- know a lot more about it before I made that type of conclusion, but let's just say that Edward Snowden has shown a light on some of these programs that a great amount of good has resulted from.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "need", "a", "lot", "--", "know", "a", "lot", "more", "about", "it", "before", "I", "made", "that", "type", "of", "conclusion", ",", "but", "let", "'s", "just", "say", "that", "Edward", "Snowden", "has", "shown", "a", "light", "on", "some", "of", "these", "programs", "that", "a", "great", "amount", "of", "good", "has", "resulted", "from", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Snowden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Why have you done this, and I know that you've read what has not been revealed to the public and you can't talk about the precise detail, but how concern should we be about what we haven't been told?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "have", "you", "done", "this", ",", "and", "I", "know", "that", "you", "'ve", "read", "what", "has", "not", "been", "revealed", "to", "the", "public", "and", "you", "ca", "n't", "talk", "about", "the", "precise", "detail", ",", "but", "how", "concern", "should", "we", "be", "about", "what", "we", "have", "n't", "been", "told", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "WRB", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Well, I think that in this case transparency is the way to go.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "in", "this", "case", "transparency", "is", "the", "way", "to", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "WRB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "Do you have any inkling and anything at all, any detail from his past that could possibly explain why this young man would shoot at point blank range Claire Davis who by all account is a delightful young lady, she's a horse lover, very loving family member, why would he even think of doing this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "inkling", "and", "anything", "at", "all", ",", "any", "detail", "from", "his", "past", "that", "could", "possibly", "explain", "why", "this", "young", "man", "would", "shoot", "at", "point", "blank", "range", "Claire", "Davis", "who", "by", "all", "account", "is", "a", "delightful", "young", "lady", ",", "she", "'s", "a", "horse", "lover", ",", "very", "loving", "family", "member", ",", "why", "would", "he", "even", "think", "of", "doing", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "I have no comment on Karl or his actions tonight I'm strictly talking about the donations and how our communities come together tonight.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "comment", "on", "Karl", "or", "his", "actions", "tonight", "I", "'m", "strictly", "talking", "about", "the", "donations", "and", "how", "our", "communities", "come", "together", "tonight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Claire Davis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Few of the students have teamed up and you're trying to raise money for what purpose?", "question_tokens": ["Few", "of", "the", "students", "have", "teamed", "up", "and", "you", "'re", "trying", "to", "raise", "money", "for", "what", "purpose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Tell me about Claire, what kind of girl is she?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "Claire", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "girl", "is", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "Claire seems -- she seemed really nice, she had a lot of friends and that she love to ride horses and all that kind of stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["Claire", "seems", "--", "she", "seemed", "really", "nice", ",", "she", "had", "a", "lot", "of", "friends", "and", "that", "she", "love", "to", "ride", "horses", "and", "all", "that", "kind", "of", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Claire"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Colorado"]}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "And in terms of Colorado and the number of incidence we've now had in the State Columbine obviously the Aurora tragedy, why do you think this mass shootings and individual shooting incidence, why Colorado?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "terms", "of", "Colorado", "and", "the", "number", "of", "incidence", "we", "'ve", "now", "had", "in", "the", "State", "Columbine", "obviously", "the", "Aurora", "tragedy", ",", "why", "do", "you", "think", "this", "mass", "shootings", "and", "individual", "shooting", "incidence", ",", "why", "Colorado", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "I really don't know why Colorado.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "do", "n't", "know", "why", "Colorado", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["State Columbine"], "LOCATION": ["Colorado", "Aurora", "Colorado"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Did you have any feeling that things weren't quite right with him?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "any", "feeling", "that", "things", "were", "n't", "quite", "right", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "You know, I couldn't really say that he was not right or anything.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "could", "n't", "really", "say", "that", "he", "was", "not", "right", "or", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Did he ever say stuff in an aggressive way which could explain perhaps some kind of agenda he may have?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "ever", "say", "stuff", "in", "an", "aggressive", "way", "which", "could", "explain", "perhaps", "some", "kind", "of", "agenda", "he", "may", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "You know, I couldn't really say.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "could", "n't", "really", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "How on earth does this happen, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["How", "on", "earth", "does", "this", "happen", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "You know, I wasn't in his shoes at the time.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "was", "n't", "in", "his", "shoes", "at", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "What else have you been hearing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "have", "you", "been", "hearing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "Were you aware of any ill will that he bore towards this decision?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "aware", "of", "any", "ill", "will", "that", "he", "bore", "towards", "this", "decision", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "Was there anything in his character would suggest an aggression or an ability to be aggressive?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "anything", "in", "his", "character", "would", "suggest", "an", "aggression", "or", "an", "ability", "to", "be", "aggressive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "He was a very outgoing person.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "a", "very", "outgoing", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Claire"]}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "How do you feel about what he did?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "what", "he", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Words can't describe how I feel for Claire and her family.", "answer_tokens": ["Words", "ca", "n't", "describe", "how", "I", "feel", "for", "Claire", "and", "her", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Did you know Claire?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "know", "Claire", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "No, sir.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Claire"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "This must be a huge shock to everybody, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "must", "be", "a", "huge", "shock", "to", "everybody", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Do you know of other students who can help him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "of", "other", "students", "who", "can", "help", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "I haven't actually spoke to the police yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "actually", "spoke", "to", "the", "police", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Is there any different or anything else?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "different", "or", "anything", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, there are a couple of important messages that you're previous guest have brought to our attention.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "are", "a", "couple", "of", "important", "messages", "that", "you", "'re", "previous", "guest", "have", "brought", "to", "our", "attention", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "POS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "And I would tell you that there are shootings within the black community that we don't cover and that the black community feels necessarily, now that's because the white-run media doesn't care what happens in the black community and I think that they're right.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "would", "tell", "you", "that", "there", "are", "shootings", "within", "the", "black", "community", "that", "we", "do", "n't", "cover", "and", "that", "the", "black", "community", "feels", "necessarily", ",", "now", "that", "'s", "because", "the", "white-run", "media", "does", "n't", "care", "what", "happens", "in", "the", "black", "community", "and", "I", "think", "that", "they", "'re", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "And we're heading for a very, very big price aren't we?", "question_tokens": ["And", "we", "'re", "heading", "for", "a", "very", ",", "very", "big", "price", "are", "n't", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "We certainly are.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "certainly", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "And if there's no winner tomorrow, then the jackpot by Friday could be $800 million which means by this following Tuesday which is Christmas or Christmas Eve, it could be $1 billion, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "there", "'s", "no", "winner", "tomorrow", ",", "then", "the", "jackpot", "by", "Friday", "could", "be", "$", "800", "million", "which", "means", "by", "this", "following", "Tuesday", "which", "is", "Christmas", "or", "Christmas", "Eve", ",", "it", "could", "be", "$", "1", "billion", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "$", "CD", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "$", "CD", "CD", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "That is correct.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday", "Tuesday"], "MONEY": ["$800 million", "$1 billion"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Christmas Eve"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "So you've made it much more difficult for Americans to actually win this right?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'ve", "made", "it", "much", "more", "difficult", "for", "Americans", "to", "actually", "win", "this", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "Well, the second side of numbers went down to one and 15.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "second", "side", "of", "numbers", "went", "down", "to", "one", "and", "15", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Are you allowed to play, Paula?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "allowed", "to", "play", ",", "Paula", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I am not.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Paula"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Is it that it's, you know, that you shouldn't -- be careful what you wish for?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "that", "it", "'s", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "you", "should", "n't", "--", "be", "careful", "what", "you", "wish", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "VB", "JJ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "Well, I figured Bud used to call it the lottery from hell.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "figured", "Bud", "used", "to", "call", "it", "the", "lottery", "from", "hell", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mike Tyson"]}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Well, didn't you have Mike Tyson on here just a little awhile ago and there are folks that by virtue of their character, their limitations, their weaknesses and vulnerabilities, you can put opportunity and money in their world.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "have", "Mike", "Tyson", "on", "here", "just", "a", "little", "awhile", "ago", "and", "there", "are", "folks", "that", "by", "virtue", "of", "their", "character", ",", "their", "limitations", ",", "their", "weaknesses", "and", "vulnerabilities", ",", "you", "can", "put", "opportunity", "and", "money", "in", "their", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Is the lottery a force for good or bad in a society like America?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "lottery", "a", "force", "for", "good", "or", "bad", "in", "a", "society", "like", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "I think the lottery is wonderful.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "lottery", "is", "wonderful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131216pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Are you going to buy a ticket for Mega Millions?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "buy", "a", "ticket", "for", "Mega", "Millions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "I'll tell you what.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "tell", "you", "what", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Mega Millions"]}}]